Elmo Roper Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1909-1972
  - Subseries C: Professional, undated, 1940-1972
    - Atlantic Union Committee
      - July - September, 1961 (Box 17:992)
      - October - December, 1961 (Box 17:993)
    - Ba, 1961 (Box 17:994)
    - Ba - Be, 1961 (Box 17:995)
    - Be - Bi, 1961 (Box 17:996)
    - Bl - Bo, 1961 (Box 17:997)
    - Br - Bu, 1961 (Box 17:998)
    - Ca, 1961 (Box 17:999)
    - Ce - Ch, 1961 (Box 17:1000)
    - Ch - Co, 1961 (Box 17:1001)
    - Co, 1961 (Box 17:1002)
    - Co - Cu, 1961 (Box 17:1003)
    - Church, Frank, 1961 (Box 17:1004)
    - CBS, 1961 (Box 17:1005)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, January - March, 1961 (Box 17:1006)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, April - October, 1961 (Box 17:1007)
    - Da, 1961 (Box 17:1008)
    - De - Du, 1961 (Box 17:1009)
    - E, 1961 (Box 17:1010)
    - Fa - Fi, 1961 (Box 17:1011)
    - Fl - Fu, 1961 (Box 17:1012)
    - Freedom House, May - July, 1961 (Box 17:1013)
    - Freedom House, September - December, 1961 (Box 17:1014)
    - Fulbright, J. W., February - August, 1961 (Box 17:1015)
    - Fulbright, J. W., September - December, 1961 (Box 17:1016)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - February, 1961 (Box 17:1017)
      - March - April, 1961 (Box 17:1018)
      - May, 1961 (Box 17:1019)
      - June, 1961 (Box 17:1020-1021)
      - July - August, 1961 (Box 17:1022)
      - October - November, 1961 (Box 17:1023)
      - December, 1961 (Box 17:1024)
    - Ga - Gl, 1961 (Box 17:1025)
    - Go - Gu, 1961 (Box 17:1026)
    - Ha, 1961 (Box 17:1027)
    - Ha - He, 1961 (Box 17:1028)
    - He - Ho, 1961 (Box 17:1029)
    - Ho - Hu, 1961 (Box 17:1030)
    - Henry Street Settlement, January - February, 1961 (Box 17:1031)
    - Henry Street Settlement, June - October, 1961 (Box 17:1032)
    - I, 1961 (Box 17:1033)
    - J, 1961 (Box 17:1034)
    - K, 1961 (Box 17:1035)
    - Kurtz, Howard, 1961 (Box 17:1036)
    - La, 1961 (Box 17:1037)
    - Le - Li, 1961 (Box 18:1038)
    - Li - Lu, 1961 (Box 18:1039)
    - M, 1961 (Box OS)
    - Ma, 1961 (Box 18:1040)
    - Ma - Mc, 1961 (Box 18:1041)
    - Mc - Me, 1961 (Box 18:1042)
    - Mo, 1961 (Box 18:1043)
    - Mo - Mu, 1961 (Box 18:1044)
    - Na - Ne, 1961 (Box 18:1045)
    - Ne - No, 1961 (Box 18:1046)
    - National Planning Association, January - August, 1961 (Box 18:1047)
    - National Planning Association, September - December, 1961 (Box 18:1048)
    - O - Pa, 1961 (Box 18:1049)
    - Pe - Pl, 1961 (Box 18:1050)
    - Po, 1961 (Box 18:1051)
    - Pr - Pu, 1961 (Box 18:1052)
    - Ra - Re, 1961 (Box 18:1053)
    - Rh - Ro, 1961 (Box 18:1054)
    - Ro - Ru, 1961 (Box 18:1055)
    - Republic Aviation Survey, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 18:1056)
    - Republic Aviation Survey, Survey/Data, 1961 (Box 18:1057)
    - Sa - Sc, 1961 (Box 18:1062)
    - Sc - Sh, 1961 (Box 18:1063)
    - Si - So, 1961 (Box 18:1064)
    - Sp - St, 1961 (Box 18:1065)
    - St, 1961 (Box 18:1066-1067)
    - Saturday Review
      - February - April, 1961 (Box 18:1068)
      - May - Jul, 1961 (Box 18:1069)
      - August, 1961 (Box 18:1070-1071)
    - T, 1961 (Box 18:1072)
    - U - V, 1961 (Box 18:1073)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1961 (Box 18:1074)
    - U.S. Citizen's Committee for NATO
      - March, 1961 (Box 18:1075)
      - April, 1961 (Box 18:1076-1079)
      - May, 1961 (Box 18:1080-1083)
      - June, 1961 (Box 18:1084-1085)
      - July, 1961 (Box 18:1086-1087)
      - August, 1961 (Box 18:1088-1089)
      - September, 1961 (Box 18:1090-1092)
      - October, 1961 (Box 18:1093-1096)
      - November, 1961 (Box 18:1097-1099)
      - December, 1961 (Box 18:1100-1102)
      - Background, 1961 (Box 18:1103-1104)
    - Wa - We, 1961 (Box 19:1105)
    - We - Wi, 1961 (Box 19:1106)
    - Wi - Wy, 1961 (Box 19:1107)
    - Williams College
      - January - February, 1961 (Box 19:1108)
      - February - March, 1961 (Box 19:1109)
      - March - May, 1961 (Box 19:1110)
      - May - June, 1961 (Box 19:1111)
      - July - September, 1961 (Box 19:1112)
      - October - December, 1961 (Box 19:1113)
    - Y, 1961 (Box 19:1114)
    - Ab - Ag, 1962 (Box 19:1115)
    - Al - Am, 1962 (Box 19:1116)
    - Am - Au, 1962 (Box 19:1117)
    - Advertising Council, 1962 (Box 19:1118)
    - American University in Cairo, 1962 (Box 19:1119)
    - Atlantic Council of the U.S.
      - January - February, 1962 (Box 19:1120)
      - February, 1962 (Box 19:1121)
      - March - April, 1962 (Box 19:1122)
      - May - June, 1962 (Box 19:1123)
      - July, 1962 (Box 19:1124)
      - July - September, 1962 (Box 19:1125)
      - October - December, 1962 (Box 19:1126)
    - Audits and Surveys, 1962 (Box 19:1127)
    - Ba, 1962 (Box 19:1128)
    - Be, 1962 (Box 19:1129)
    - Bi - Bl, 1962 (Box 19:1130)
    - Bo - Br, 1962 (Box 19:1131)
    - Br - Bu, 1962 (Box 19:1132)
    - Ca, 1962 (Box 19:1133)
    - Ca - Ce, 1962 (Box 19:1134)
    - Ch, 1962 (Box 19:1135)
    - Ch - Co, 1962 (Box 19:1136)
    - Co, 1962 (Box 19:1137)
    - Co - Cr, 1962 (Box 19:1138)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 19:1139)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, Background, 1962 (Box 19:1140)
    - Connecticut Committee on Libraries
      - January - March, 1962 (Box 19:1141)
      - March, 1962 (Box 19:1142-1143)
      - April, 1962 (Box 19:1144)
    - Connecticut Committee on Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 19:1145)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, January - April, 1962 (Box 19:1146)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, May - December, 1962 (Box 19:1147)
    - Da - De, 1962 (Box 19:1148)
    - De, 1962 (Box 19:1149)
    - De - Di, 1962 (Box 19:1150)
    - E, 1962 (Box 19:1151)
    - Fa - Fi, 1962 (Box 19:1152)
    - Fi - Fu, 1962 (Box 19:1153)
    - Freedom House, 1962 (Box 19:1154)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - February, 1962 (Box 19:1155)
      - February, 1962 (Box 19:1156)
      - March, 1962 (Box 19:1157)
      - March - April, 1962 (Box 19:1158)
      - May - June, 1962 (Box 19:1159)
      - July - August, 1962 (Box 19:1160)
      - September, 1962 (Box 19:1161)
      - October - December, 1962 (Box 19:1162)
    - Ga - Go, 1962 (Box 19:1163)
    - Gr, 1962 (Box 19:1164)
    - Ha, 1962 (Box 19:1165)
    - Ha - He, 1962 (Box 19:1166)
    - He, 1962 (Box 19:1167)
    - He - Ho, 1962 (Box 19:1168)
    - Ho - Hu, 1962 (Box 19:1169)
    - I - J, 1962 (Box 19:1170)
    - Ka - Ke, 1962 (Box 19:1171)
    - Ki - Ku, 1962 (Box 19:1172)
    - La - Le, 1962 (Box 19:1173)
    - Li - Ly, 1962 (Box 19:1174)
    - Ma, 1962 (Box 19:1175)
    - Mc - Mi, 1962 (Box 19:1176)
    - Mo, 1962 (Box 20:1177)
    - Mo - Mu, 1962 (Box 20:1178)
    - Market Research Council, 1962 (Box 20:1179)
    - Na - Ne, 1962 (Box 20:1180)
    - Ne - No, 1962 (Box 20:1181)
    - National Planning Association, 1962 (Box 20:1182)
    - O - Pa, 1962 (Box 20:1183)
    - Ph - Pl, 1962 (Box 20:1184)
    - Po, 1962 (Box 20:1185)
    - Public Pulse
      - January - April, 1962 (Box 20:1186)
      - May - July, 1962 (Box 20:1187)
      - August - September, 1962 (Box 20:1188)
    - R - Ro, 1962 (Box 20:1189)
    - Ro 1962 (Box 20:1190)
    - Roper [business], 1962 (Box 20:1191)
    - Sa, 1962 (Box 20:1193)
    - Sc - Sk, 1962 (Box 20:1194)
    - Sm - St, 1962 (Box 20:1195)
    - St, 1962 (Box 20:1196)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1962 (Box 20:1197)
    - Ta - Te, 1962 (Box 20:1198)
    - Th - Ti, 1962 (Box 20:1199)
    - Un, 1962 (Box 20:1200)
    - Un - Uv, 1962 (Box 20:1201)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1962 (Box 20:1202)
    - U.S. Citizen's Commission for NATO
      - January, 1962 (Box 20:1203-1204)
      - January - February, 1962 (Box 20:1205)
      - February, 1962 (Box 20:1206-1207)
      - February - March, 1962 (Box 20:1208)
      - March, 1962 (Box 20:1209-1210)
      - March - May, 1962 (Box 20:1211)
      - June - July, 1962 (Box 20:1212)
      - Documents, 1962 (Box 20:1213-1221)
    - V, 1962 (Box 20:1222)
    - Wa - We, 1962 (Box 20:1223)
    - Wi, 1962 (Box 20:1224)
    - Wi - Wo, 1962 (Box 20:1225)
    - Wo - Wr, 1962 (Box 20:1226)
    - Williams College
      - January, 1962 (Box 20:1227)
      - January - February, 1962 (Box 20:1228)
      - February - March, 1962 (Box 20:1229)
      - April - May, 1962 (Box 20:1230)
      - June - July, 1962 (Box 20:1231)
      - August, 1962 (Box 20:1232)
      - August - September, 1962 (Box 20:1233)
      - September - November, 1962 (Box 20:1234)
    - Wyatt, Wilson
      - March - May, 1962 (Box 20:1235)
      - May - June, 1962 (Box 20:1236)
      - June - November, 1962 (Box 20:1237)
    - Y - Z, 1962 (Box 20:1238)
    - Ad - Am, 1963 (Box 20:1239)
    - Am - Au, 1963 (Box 20:1240)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1963 (Box 20:1241)
    - American Political Science Association, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 20:1242)
    - American Political Science Association, Background, 1963 (Box 20:1243)
    - American University in Cairo, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 20:1244)
    - American University in Cairo, Background, 1963 (Box 20:1245)
    - Atlantic Council of the U.S.
      - January - April, 1963 (Box 20:1246)
      - May, 1963 (Box 20:1247)
      - June - July, 1963 (Box 20:1248)
      - July, 1963 (Box 21:1249)
      - August - September, 1963 (Box 21:1250)
      - October, 1963 (Box 21:1251)
      - November, 1963 (Box 21:1252-1253)
      - December, 1963 (Box 21:1254)
      - Background, 1963 (Box 21:1255)
    - Atlas, 1963 (Box 21:1256)
    - B, 1963 (Box OS)
    - Ba - Be, 1963 (Box 21:1257)
    - Be - Bi, 1963 (Box 21:1258)
    - Bo, 1963 (Box 21:1259)
    - Br - Bu, 1963 (Box 21:1260)
    - Ca, 1963 (Box 21:1261)
    - Ce, 1963 (Box 21:1262)
    - Ch, 1963 (Box 21:1263)
    - Ci - Co, 1963 (Box 21:1264)
    - Co, 1963 (Box 21:1265)
    - Co - Cu, 1963 (Box 21:1266)
    - Connecticut Committee on Libraries, 1963 (Box 21:1267)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, January - August, 1963 (Box 21:1268)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, August - December, 1963 (Box 21:1269)
    - Da - De, 1963 (Box 21:1270)
    - De - Dr, 1963 (Box 21:1271)
    - Ea - El, 1963 (Box 21:1272)
    - En - Es, 1963 (Box 21:1273)
    - Fa - Fi, 1963 (Box 21:1274)
    - Fi - Fu, 1963 (Box 21:1275)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January, 1963 (Box 21:1276)
      - January - February, 1963 (Box 21:1277)
      - March - August, 1963 (Box 21:1278)
      - August - December, 1963 (Box 21:1279)
    - Ga, 1963 (Box 21:1280)
    - Ga - Go, 1963 (Box 21:1281)
    - Gr, 1963 (Box 21:1282)
    - Gr - Gu, 1963 (Box 21:1283)
    - Ha, 1963 (Box 21:1284)
    - He, 1963 (Box 21:1285)
    - He - Ho, 1963 (Box 21:1286)
    - Ho - Hu, 1963 (Box 21:1287)
    - I - J, 1963 (Box 21:1288)
    - Ka - Ke, 1963 (Box 21:1289)
    - Kr - Ku, 1963 (Box 21:1290)
    - La - Le, 1963 (Box 21:1291)
    - Li - Lu, 1963 (Box 21:1292)
    - Ma, 1963 (Box 21:1293-1294)
    - Mc - Mo, 1963 (Box 21:1295)
    - Mo - Mu, 1963 (Box 21:1296)
    - Na, 1963 (Box 21:1297)
    - Ne, 1963 (Box 21:1298)
    - Ne - Ny, 1963 (Box 21:1299)
    - National Planning Association, April - July, 1963 (Box 21:1300)
    - National Planning Association, July - December, 1963 (Box 21:1301)
    - O, 1963 (Box 21:1302)
    - Pa, 1963 (Box 21:1303-1304)
    - Pe - Ph, 1963 (Box 21:1305)
    - Pl - Po, 1963 (Box 21:1306)
    - Po - Pu, 1963 (Box 21:1307)
    - Q - Ri, 1963 (Box 21:1308)
    - Ri - Ro, 1963 (Box 21:1309)
    - Ro, 1963 (Box 21:1310)
    - Roper [business], 1963 (Box 21:1311)
    - Sa, 1963 (Box 22:1312)
    - Sc - Se, 1963 (Box 22:1313)
    - Sh - Sn, 1963 (Box 22:1314)
    - Sp - St, 1963 (Box 22:1315)
    - St, 1963 (Box 22:1316-1317)
    - Senators' Party
      - July - September, 1963 (Box 22:1318)
      - September - October, 1963 (Box 22:1319)
      - October, 1963 (Box 22:1320)
      - October - November, 1963 (Box 22:1321)
    - T, 1963 (Box 22:1322)
    - This Week
      - January - June, 1963 (Box 22:1323)
      - August - December, 1963 (Box 22:1324)
    - Un, 1963 (Box 22:1325)
    - Un - Ur, 1963 (Box 22:1326)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1963 (Box 22:1327)
    - Wa - Wb, 1963 (Box 22:1328)
    - We, 1963 (Box 22:1329)
    - We - Wi, 1963 (Box 22:1330)
    - Wr - Z, 1963 (Box 22:1331)
    - Williams College
      - February - June, 1963 (Box 22:1332)
      - July, 1963 (Box 22:1333)
      - August - September, 1963 (Box 22:1334)
      - September - October, 1963 (Box 22:1335)
      - November - December, 1963 (Box 22:1336)
    - Ab - Al, 1964 (Box 22:1337)
    - Am, 1964 (Box 22:1338-1339)
    - An - Au, 1964 (Box 22:1340)
    - Advertising Council, 1964 (Box 22:1341)
    - American Political Science Association, January - June, 1964 (Box 22:1342)
    - American Political Science Association, Background, June, 1964 (Box 22:1343)
    - Atlantic Council of the U.S.
      - January - March, 1964 (Box 22:1344)
      - April - May, 1964 (Box 22:1345)
      - June, 1964 (Box 22:1346-1347)
      - July, 1964 (Box 22:1348)
      - August - October, 1964 (Box 22:1349)
      - October, 1964 (Box 22:1350)
      - November, 1964 (Box 22:1351)
      - December, 1964 (Box 22:1352)
    - Ba, 1964 (Box 22:1353-1354)
    - Be - Bi, 1964 (Box 22:1355)
    - Bl, 1964 (Box 22:1356)
    - Bo - Br, 1964 (Box 22:1357)
    - Bu, 1964 (Box 22:1358)
    - Ca - Ch, 1964 (Box 22:1359)
    - Ci - Co, 1964 (Box 22:1360)
    - Cr - Cu, 1964 (Box 22:1361)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, January - June, 1964 (Box 22:1362)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, June - November, 1964 (Box 22:1363)
    - D, 1964 (Box 22:1364)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity
      - January - February, 1964 (Box 22:1365)
      - April - May, 1964 (Box 22:1366)
      - May - June, 1964 (Box 22:1367)
      - June - September, 1964 (Box 22:1368)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., 1964 (Box OS)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., February - October, 1964 (Box 22:1369)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., October - December, undated, 1964 (Box 22:1370)
    - E - Fl, 1964 (Box 22:1371)
    - Fo - Fu, 1964 (Box 22:1372)
    - Freedom House, 1964 (Box 22:1373)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - April, 1964 (Box 22:1374)
      - April - June, 1964 (Box 22:1375)
      - July - October, 1964 (Box 22:1376)
      - November - December, 1964 (Box 22:1377)
    - G, 1964 (Box OS)
    - Ga - Go, 1964 (Box 22:1378)
    - Go - Gr, 1964 (Box 22:1379)
    - Ha, 1964 (Box 22:1380-1381)
    - He, 1964 (Box 23:1382)
    - He - Ho, 1964 (Box 23:1383)
    - Ho, 1964 (Box 23:1384)
    - Ho - Hu, 1964 (Box 23:1385)
    - Haug Associates, January - March, 1964 (Box 23:1386)
    - Haug Associates, July - November, undated, 1964 (Box 23:1387)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, 1964 (Box 23:1388)
    - I, 1964 (Box OS)
    - I, 1964 (Box 23:1389)
    - Ja - Jo, 1964 (Box 23:1390)
    - Jo - JU, 1964 (Box 23:1391)
    - Ka - Ke, 1964 (Box 23:1392)
    - Ke - Ku, 1964 (Box 23:1393)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., January - February, 1964 (Box 23:1394)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., March - August, 1964 (Box 23:1395)
    - Kurtz, Howard G., December, undated, 1964 (Box 23:1396)
    - La, 1964 (Box 23:1397)
    - Le - Li, 1964 (Box 23:1398)
    - Li - Lu, 1964 (Box 23:1399)
    - Ma, 1964 (Box 23:1400)
    - Ma - Mc, 1964 (Box 23:1401)
    - Mc - Me, 1964 (Box 23:1402)
    - Mi - Mo, 1964 (Box 23:1403)
    - Mo - Mu, 1964 (Box 23:1404)
    - Na, 1964 (Box 23:1405)
    - Na - Ne, 1964 (Box 23:1406)
    - Ne - Nu, 1964 (Box 23:1407)
    - National Planning Association, January - February, 1964 (Box 23:1408)
    - National Planning Association, March - October, 1964 (Box 23:1409)
    - Of, 1964 (Box 23:1410)
    - Of - Or, 1964 (Box 23:1411)
    - Pa, 1964 (Box 23:1412)
    - Pe - Pr, 1964 (Box 23:1413)
    - Pr - Pu, 1964 (Box 23:1414)
    - Re - Ri, 1964 (Box 23:1415)
    - Ro - Ru, 1964 (Box 23:1416)
    - Roper [personal/family/business], 1964 (Box 23:1418)
    - Sa - Sc, 1964 (Box 23:1419)
    - Sa - Sh, 1964 (Box 23:1420)
    - Si - Sp, 1964 (Box 23:1421)
    - St, 1964 (Box 23:1422-1423)
    - Sw - Sy, 1964 (Box 23:1424)
    - Sturday Review, February - September, 1964 (Box 23:1425)
    - Sturday Review, October - December, 1964 (Box 23:1426)
    - Ta - Th, 1964 (Box 23:1427)
    - Th - Tu, 1964 (Box 23:1428)
    - Ul - Un, 1964 (Box 23:1429)
    - Un, 1964 (Box 23:1430)
    - Un - V, 1964 (Box 23:1431)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1964 (Box 23:1432)
    - Wa - We, 1964 (Box 23:1433)
    - We, 1964 (Box 23:1434)
    - Wi, 1964 (Box 23:1435)
    - Wo - Y, 1964 (Box 23:1436)
    - Williams College, January - May, 1964 (Box 23:1437)
    - Williams College, May - November, 1964 (Box 23:1438)
    - Ac - Ag, 1965 (Box 23:1439)
    - Am, 1965 (Box 23:1440)
    - An - As, 1965 (Box 23:1441)
    - Atlantic Council of the U.S.
      - January - March, 1965 (Box 23:1442)
      - April - July, 1965 (Box 23:1443)
      - September - October, 1965 (Box 23:1444)
      - November - December, 1965 (Box 23:1445)
    - Ba, 1965 (Box 23:1446)
    - Be - Bl, 1965 (Box 23:1447)
    - Br - Bu, 1965 (Box 23:1448)
    - Ca, 1965 (Box 23:1450)
    - Ca - Ce, 1965 (Box 23:1451)
    - Ch, 1965 (Box 23:1452-1453)
    - Cl - Co, 1965 (Box 23:1454)
    - Co - Cu, 1965 (Box 23:1455)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, March - July, 1965 (Box 23:1456)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, August - December, 1965 (Box 23:1457)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, June - October, 1965 (Box 23:1458)
    - Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights, Background, 1965 (Box 23:1459)
    - D - Di, 1965 (Box 24:1460)
    - Di - Du, 1965 (Box 24:1461)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity, 1965 (Box 24:1462)
    - Ea - En, 1965 (Box 24:1463)
    - En - Ev, 1965 (Box 24:1464)
    - Fe - Fi, 1965 (Box 24:1465)
    - Fo, 1965 (Box 24:1466)
    - Fr, 1965 (Box 24:1467)
    - Fund for the Republic
      - January - February, 1965 (Box 24:1468)
      - Background, 1965 (Box 24:1469)
      - February - August, 1965 (Box 24:1470)
      - September - October, 1965 (Box 24:1471)
      - October - December, 1965 (Box 24:1472)
      - December, 1965 (Box 24:1473)
    - Ga, 1965 (Box 24:1474)
    - Ga - Go, 1965 (Box 24:1475)
    - Gr, 1965 (Box 24:1476)
    - Ha, 1965 (Box 24:1477-1478)
    - He, 1965 (Box 24:1479)
    - Hi - Ho, 1965 (Box 24:1480)
    - Ho - Hu, 1965 (Box 24:1481)
    - Hutchins Tribute Dinner
      - December, 1964 (Box 24:1482)
      - December - February, 1964-1965 (Box 24:1483)
      - February, 1965 (Box 24:1484)
      - February - March, 1965 (Box 24:1485)
      - Background, 1965 (Box 24:1486)
    - I - J, 1965 (Box 24:1487)
    - Ke, 1965 (Box 24:1488)
    - Kr - Ku, 1965 (Box 24:1489)
    - Kefauver Memorial Foundation, January - March, 1965 (Box 24:1490)
    - Kefauver Memorial Foundation, December, 1965 (Box 24:1491)
    - L, 1965 (Box 24:1492)
    - Ma, 1965 (Box 24:1493-1494)
    - Mc - Mu, 1965 (Box 24:1495)
    - Na, 1965 (Box 24:1496-1497)
    - Na - Ne, 1965 (Box 24:1498)
    - National Library Week, 1965 (Box 24:1499)
    - National Planning Association, January - July, 1965 (Box 24:1500)
    - National Planning Association, September - October, 1965 (Box 24:1501)
    - Nylock Corporation, January - March, 1965 (Box 24:1502)
    - Nylock Corporation, April - June, 1965 (Box 24:1503)
    - Of - Oh, 1965 (Box 24:1504)
    - Op - Or, 1965 (Box 24:1505)
    - Pa - Pi, 1965 (Box 24:1506)
    - Pl - Pu, 1965 (Box 24:1507)
    - Ra - Ri, 1965 (Box 24:1508)
    - Ro - Ry, 1965 (Box 24:1509)
    - Roper [business/farm], 1965 (Box 24:1510)
    - Roper Center, 1965 (Box 24:1511)
    - Roper--European trip, 1965 (Box 24:1512)
    - Roper--Washington Dinner, 1965 (Box 24:1514)
    - Sa - Si, 1965 (Box 24:1515)
    - Sh - So, 1965 (Box 24:1516)
    - St, 1965 (Box 24:1517)
    - St - Sz, 1965 (Box 24:1518)
    - Saturday Review, January - August, 1965 (Box 24:1519)
    - Saturday Review, August - November, 1965 (Box 24:1520)
    - Spiegel, Inc., 1965 (Box 24:1521)
    - Ta - Ti, 1965 (Box 24:1522)
    - Ti - Tu, 1965 (Box 24:1523)
    - U - V, 1965 (Box 24:1524)
    - Umpawaug Company, 1965 (Box 24:1525)
    - University of Nebraska
      - January - February, 1965 (Box 24:1526)
      - March - May, 1965 (Box 24:1527)
      - June - December, 1965 (Box 24:1528)
    - Wa - Wi, 1965 (Box 24:1529)
    - Wl - Wy, 1965 (Box 24:1530)
    - Y - Z, 1965 (Box 24:1531)
    - Ab - Ad, 1966 (Box 24:1542)
    - Am - Ay, 1966 (Box 24:1533)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1966 (Box 24:1534)
    - Advertising Council, 1966 (Box 24:1535)
    - American University in Cairo, 1966 (Box 24:1536)
    - Atlantic Council
      - January - April, 1966 (Box 25:1537)
      - June - December, 1966 (Box 25:1538)
      - Background, 1966 (Box 25:1539-1540)
    - Ba - Be, 1966 (Box 25:1541)
    - Bi - Bl, 1966 (Box 25:1542)
    - Bo - Bu, 1966 (Box 25:1543)
    - Baldwin, W. Orville, January - March, 1966 (Box 25:1544)
    - Baldwin, W. Orville, April - December, 1966 (Box 25:1545)
    - Benton, William, 1966 (Box 25:1546)
    - Ca, 1966 (Box 25:1547)
    - Ce - Chr, 1966 (Box 25:1548)
    - Chu - Cle, 1966 (Box 25:1549)
    - Cli - Coo, 1966 (Box 25:1550)
    - Cor - Cu, 1966 (Box 25:1551)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
      - February, 1966 (Box 25:1552)
      - March, 1966 (Box 25:1553)
      - April, 1966 (Box 25:1554)
      - May, 1966 (Box 25:1555)
      - June - July, 1966 (Box 25:1556)
      - August, 1966 (Box 25:1557)
      - September, 1966 (Box 25:1558)
      - September - October, 1966 (Box 25:1559)
      - November, 1966 (Box 25:1560)
      - Background, 1966 (Box 25:1561-1562)
    - Connecticut Civil Rights Commission, 1966 (Box 25:1563)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1966 (Box 25:1564)
    - Da - Dem, 1966 (Box 25:1565)
    - Dew - Dod, 1966 (Box 25:1566)
    - Dou, 1966 (Box 25:1567)
    - Dri - Du, 1966 (Box 25:1568)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity
      - January - February, 1966 (Box 25:1569)
      - March - April, 1966 (Box 25:1570)
      - May - November, 1966 (Box 25:1571)
    - E, 1966 (Box 25:1572)
    - Fa - Fie, 1966 (Box 25:1573)
    - Fie - Fo, 1966 (Box 25:1574)
    - Fr - Fu, 1966 (Box 25:1575)
    - Finch, Robert H., January - May, 1966 (Box 25:1576)
    - Finch, Robert H., August - November, 1966 (Box 25:1577)
    - Fortune Survey, 1966 (Box 25:1578-1579)
    - Ga - Gre, 1966 (Box 25:1580)
    - Gre - Gru, 1966 (Box 25:1581)
    - Garwood, Ellen (Mrs. St. John), January - March, 1966 (Box 25:1582)
    - Garwood, Ellen (Mrs. St. John), April - June, 1966 (Box 25:1583)
    - Garwood, Ellen (Mrs. St. John), July - October, 1966 (Box 25:1584)
    - Ha, 1966 (Box 25:1585-1586)
    - He, 1966 (Box 25:1587)
    - Hi, 1966 (Box 25:1588)
    - Ho, 1966 (Box 25:1589-1590)
    - Hu, 1966 (Box 25:1591)
    - Henry Street Settlement, 1966 (Box 25:1592)
    - I - J, 1966 (Box 25:1593)
    - K, 1966 (Box 25:1594)
    - Kefauver Memorial Foundation, 1966 (Box 25:1595)
    - La - Li, 1966 (Box 25:1596)
    - Lo - Lu, 1966 (Box 25:1597)
    - Ma - Mc, 1966 (Box 25:1598)
    - Mc - Mi, 1966 (Box 25:1599)
    - Mon - Moo, 1966 (Box 25:1600)
    - Mor - Mu, 1966 (Box 25:1601)
    - N, 1966 (Box 25:1602)
    - National Planning Assoication, 1966 (Box 25:1603-1604)
    - O, 1966 (Box 25:1605)
    - P, 1966 (Box 25:1606)
    - Population Crisis Committee, 1966 (Box 25:1607-1610)
    - Re - Ri, 1966 (Box 26:1611)
    - Rob - Roo, 1966 (Box 26:1612)
    - Ros - Ru, 1966 (Box 26:1613)
    - Roper Center, Roper [business/farm], 1966 (Box 26:1614)
    - Sa - Sc, 1966 (Box 26:1616)
    - Si - Sp, 1966 (Box 26:1617)
    - St - Su, 1966 (Box 26:1618)
    - Saturday Review, 1966 (Box 26:1619)
    - Standard Oil Leaders survey, 1966 (Box 26:1620-1622)
    - Ta - Th, 1966 (Box 26:1623)
    - Ti - To, 1966 (Box 26:1624)
    - Tr, 1966 (Box 26:1625)
    - U, 1966 (Box 26:1626)
    - Umpawaug Company
      - January - April, 1966 (Box 26:1627)
      - May - July, 1966 (Box 26:1628)
      - August - December, 1966 (Box 26:1629)